Guide to the Frederick Fried Coney Island collection
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Photographs, 1894-2001 undated
  - Subseries I.1: Photographic Prints, 1894-2001 undated
    - Carousels
      - Carousel with Illions carvings at William F. Mangels’ Midway, Stubbman Building (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Carousel with horses by William F. Mangels and Marcus Charles Illions, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Carousel with horses by William F. Mangels and Marcus Charles Illions, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Carousel with horses by William F. Mangels and Marcus Charles Illions, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Carousel with horses by William F. Mangels and Marcus Charles Illions (Glen Echo, Maryland), 1912 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Forty-four foot carousel (Glen Echo, Maryland), 1912 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Carousel, W.F. Mangels Company, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Carousel with horse carved by Marcus Charles Illions, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - William Manchester Keating, George Green's “Four-a-brest” Bantams carousel on the carnival ground (Glasgow, Scotland), 1910 [This ride was sold to Coney Island, New York, Amusement Company, during 1913 and was reported to be there in 1950 but minus its top cover] (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Carousel, William F. Mangels Carousel Works, John J. Hurley’s Hurley’s Hurdlers (Revere Beach, Massachusets), undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Kiddie Carousel built by William F. Mangels, Coney Island (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Three-row carousel by William F. Mangels (Glen Echo, Maryland, 1912) (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Fifty-foot diameter carousel, with forty galloping horses, twenty-eight standing horses, four double chariots, eighty-four-passenger capacity, for $11,000, from William F. Mangels catalog, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Carousel, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Carousel, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Kister's Carousel, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - W.F. Mangels Company Carousel Works, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Coney Island Chamber of Commerce, Model of Sassek's Balloon Carousel, which operated in Coney Island in 1886 in William F. Mangel's Museum of Public Recreation, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Carousel and Swan Ride, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Carousel, Willow Grove Park (Willow Grove, Pennsylvania), undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Carousel with signs reading "Carousell Tickets Here,” undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Sepia print with carousel passengers, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Columbia Carousel, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Columbia Carousel with machinery by William F. Mangels and horses carved by Charles Looff, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - “Mangels' Three-Row Kiddie Carousel,” undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Carousel tiger carved by Marcus Illions, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Ink drawing of carousel at Willow Grove Park (Willow Grove, Pennsylvania), undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Krause's portable carousel by William F. Mangels, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, William F. Mangels carousel with horses carved by Marcus Illions, from W.F. Mangels Company catalog, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Two-row portable and steam-driven carousel by William F. Mangels with horses and chariots carved by Marcus Illions, from W.F. Mangels Company catalog, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - William F. Mangels carousel, Willow Grove Park (Willow Grove, Pennsylvania), 1910 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, William F. Mangels portable carousel, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - William F. Mangels portable carousel, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Pinto Brothers, Pinto Brothers carousel for children, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Savin Rock Carousel, built by William F. Mangels for Frank Wilcox Company, (West Haven, Connecticut), undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - William F. Mangels carousel, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - William F. Mangels carousel, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - William F. Mangels carousel, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - William F. Mangels carousel, Riverside Amusement Park (Agawam, Massachusetts), undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - W.F. Mangels Company’s “Combination Palace Galloping Horse Carousel,” Willow Grove Park (Willow Grove, Pennsylvania), 1910 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - “William F. Mangels' Galloping Horse Carousel,” undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - William F. Mangels' Galloping Horse Carousel, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, William F. Mangels’ portable carousal (Sharon, Connecticut), undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Savin Rock Carousel, built by William F. Mangels for Frank Wilcox Company, (West Haven, Connecticut), undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Chariots
      - Chariot to Dreamland, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Chariot, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Dreamland
      - William C. Meinsch, Dreamland bathing pavilion, observation tower, Dreamland tower, and beach, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - William C. Meinsch, Dreamland bathing pavilion, observation tower, and Shoot the Chutes, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - “Fighting the Flames” ride and Dreamland tower, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Dreamland Park tower at night, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - “Trip through Switzerland” rollercoaster, Dreamland Park, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - William C. Meinsch, Dreamland tower and building at night, before 1911 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Dreamland, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Edio Photos, Circus performers and elephant at Dreamland, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Photograph of painting of L. A. Thompson’s Marine Scenic Railway at Dreamland, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Feltma n's Gardens
      - E.E. Rutter, Feltman's Gardens at Surf Avenue and West Tenth Street decorated for Mardi Gras with view of carousel, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - E.E. Rutter, Feltman's Gardens reception area, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - E.E. Rutter, Feltman's Gardens reception room, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Feltman's Gardens, outdoor diners at night, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - E.E. Rutter, Feltman's Gardens, outdoor diners, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Feltman's Gardens, outdoor diners, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Performers in Bavarian dress on stage in beer garden at Feltman's Gardens, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Feltman's Gardens, outdoor diners, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Coney Island Times, View from above of Feltman's Gardens, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Coney Island Times, Performers in Bavarian dress on stage in beer garden at Feltman's Gardens, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - E.E. Rutter, Tables at Feltman's Gardens, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Unloading barrels at Feltman's Gardens, circa 1920 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Fires
      - Damage and debris after the Bowery Fire (Coney Island, New York), 1895 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Remains of the Old Mill after the Bowery Fire (Coney Island, New York), 1895 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Floats and Parade Wagons
      - Electricity/lighting float, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Carnival wagon at Coney Island, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Coney Island Mardi Gras parade float with the Lusitania, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Coney Island Mardi Gras parade float with presidential candidates, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Coney Island/Luna Park (The Whip) parade wagon, with William F. Mangels in dark cap, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Cottage and skyscraper float, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Floats and parade wagons, 1904 undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Float with men on horseback, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Coney Island Mardi Gras parade 'Heroes' float, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Military-themed, patriotic float with Uncle Sam and an American eagle, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Floats and parade wagons, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Oxcart wagon, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Stork float at night, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Women on “Gay '90s-looking float,” undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - “Flying Turns Coaster,” 1929 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Freakshow
      - JoJo the Dog Boy standing on nails, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - JoJo the Dog Boy posed by a tree, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - JoJo the Dog Boy, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - JoJo the Dog Boy, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - JoJo the Dog Boy, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - JoJo the Dog Boy, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Orange Chicken Gallery, “Freaks, Geeks, and Carnies,” The Orange Chicken Gallery (New York, New York) exhibition brochure, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Orange Chicken Gallery, “Freaks, Geeks, and Carnies,” The Orange Chicken Gallery (New York, New York) exhibition brochure, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Orange Chicken Gallery, “Freaks, Geeks, and Carnies,” The Orange Chicken Gallery (New York, New York) exhibition brochure, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - A pair of dwarf boxers, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Group of five men, including Zip the Pinhead and JoJo the Dog Boy, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Violet and Daisy, English Siamese twins, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Greater Sheesley show wagons, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hotels
      - Albemarle Hotel (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Building the Oriental Hotel (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Horn-Coney Island, Ground-breaking ceremony for Half-Moon Hotel (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Hotel Park Plaza (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Hunter's Hotel (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Stratton's Hotel (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Incubation Institute
      - Haynes-Provost Studio, Dr. Martin Couney’s “Incubator Baby Exhibits” at the New York World's Fair, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Dr. Martin Couney’s “Incubator Baby Exhibit” on the Boardwalk at Coney Island, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Coney Island Times, Attendants at the “Incubator Baby Exhibit” at Coney Island, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Eric Schaal, Dr. Martin Couney demonstrates the mental and physical development of incubated infants to the American Pediatric Society at the New York World's Fair, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Three sets of twins, patients at the Incubation Institution at Coney Island, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - “After feeding, the baby is returned to incubator by Dr. Martin Arthur Couney's daughter Hildegard, an R.N. assistant, to head nurse Louise Richt, the latter having been with the Incubation Institution since is inception in 1897” undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - “Baby graduates from incubation to nursery and is weaned from mother's milk to bottle feeding before returning to parents, Coney Island,” undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Dr. Martin Couney and others, included nurses and babies entrance to the Incubation Institution (Coney Island, New York), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - “Dr. Martin Arthur Couney holding baby that Weighs less than 2 pounds,” undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - “Dr. Martin Arthur Couney recording the daily weight to assess daily gain of the infant,” undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Two babies and two attendants, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - An Incubation Institute graduate of 1939 greets Dr. Couney, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Luna Park
      - General Electric Publication Bureau, Luna Park: Night view of “Somali Land” and The Tickler (Coney Island, New York) showing “1,000 watt Edison Mazda Lamps in Outdoor Diffusing Fixtures,” undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - “Topsy, elephant at Luna Park who killed 3 men in 3 years, including her handler and was put to death by electrocution by Thomas Edison's employees,” 1903 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Cars, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Checkers, circa 1910 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Coney Island/Luna Park (The Whip) parade wagon, with William F. Mangels in dark cap, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - General Electric Publication Bureau, View of the lagoon, “with 750 and 1,000 watt Mazda lamps in diffusing balls for general illumination,” circa 1913 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Entrance to The Tickler, undated (3 images) (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Entrance to The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Entrance to The Whip, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - The great fire of 1946 1946 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - View showing the Luna Ride and “Incubator Baby Exhibits,” undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Charles Nesensohn, View showing the Luna Ride and “Incubator Baby Exhibits,” undated (5 images) (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - American Museum of Public Recreation, Frederic W. Thompson exhibition at William F. Mangels' American Museum of Public Recreation, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Helter Skelter ride, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - The Whip and the Crazy Village rides, undated (2 images) (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Men in bowler hats ride The Whip, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Visitors about to ride The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Visitors entering and leaving The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Visitors waiting to ride The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Visitors riding The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Visitors entering and leaving The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Visitors riding The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Visitors preparing to ride The Tickler, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - The Teaser, circa 1910 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - The Tickler, undated (4 images) (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - The Whip, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - The Whip in a rural setting, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - The Whip at a town carnival, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - The Whip indoors, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - “Elephant carving,” undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - American Museum of Public Recreation, “Elephant carving,” undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - The Whip, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - The Whip and Ferris Wheel, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - “Topsy, elephant lying dead at Luna Park--killed three people in three years, including her handler and was put to death by electrocution by Thomas Edison's employees, Coney Island,” 1903 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Mangels, William F.
      - American Museum of Public Recreation, Mangels’ model of the “Loop-the-Loop” roller coaster, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Mangels’ model of the “Loop-the-Loop” roller coaster, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Mangels’ model of the “Loop-the-Loop” roller coaster, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Mangels’ model of an unidentified amusement park ride, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - American Museum of Public Recreation, Mangels’ model of the “Pleasure Wheel” Ferris Wheel, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - W.F. Mangels Company, Mangels’ model of a swing ride, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Mangels’ model of an electric pleasure railway, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Photograph of William F. Mangels’ model-making shop, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - American Museum of Public Recreation, circa 1948 undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Display of carousel animals, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Eddie Cantor at the American Museum of Public Recreation, circa 1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Photographic negatives showing Eddie Cantor at the American Museum of Public Recreation, circa 1948 [to be removed to a separate box] (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Carousel lions, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Interior of W.F. Mangels Company shop, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Mangels: Man in Aero-Locomotive, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - View of “Carousell works,” undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - View of the “Little ‘Brownie’ Roller Coaster” in the W.F. Mangels Company shop, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Model-making shop of the W.F. Mangels Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - View of the Kiddie Coaster in the W.F. Mangels Company carousel shop, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Dolls sit a model swing ride, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Models of “Senegas Amusement Devices,” undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Kiddie Wheel, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Kiddie Wheel, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - “Little ‘Brownie’ Roller Coaster,” undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - “Little ‘Brownie’ Roller Coaster,” undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - “Little ‘Brownie’ Roller Coaster,” 1931 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - The Teaser, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Aero-locomotive, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - “Little ‘Brownie’ Roller Coaster,” undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Wiliam F. Mangels Carousel Works, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Mangels, William F., rides designed by, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Various amusement rides at the W.F. Mangels Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - W.F. Mangels Company model shop, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - W.F. Mangels Company model shop, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - William F. Mangles Company model shop, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - William F. Mangles Company model shop, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - “William F. Mangel's Ticket Box for Ruben and Cherry Shows,” 1930 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Music Hall--Henderson's music hall, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Panoramas and Crowd Shots
      - Band and crowd in front of Surf Avenue Opera House, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Beach at Coney Island, circa 1920 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Bay Shore Park, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Coney Island with the Dodgem in the foreground, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Rockaway Beach, 1901 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - The Bowery, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Ward Avenue, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Ocean Parkway looking toward the boat landing, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Surf Avenue, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Sheepshead Bay, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - East Lake Park (Birmingham, Alabama), undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Lundy's Restaurant, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - White Rose Park (York, Pennsylvania), undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - “In Front of Miss Rockaway,” undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Colored engraving of the Brooklyn seashore, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Boardwalk and the Turkish Theater, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - “Boardwalk at Coney Island, Looking East from Mooney's Bath at West Eighth Street,” 1923 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - “Boys carrying $20,000 in money bags at Coney Island, on way to the bank on July 5th, 1903” (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Coney Island Beach, circa 1920 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Coney Island lifeguards, circa 1905 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Coney Island, circa 1905 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - View of Coney Island showing the House of Nonsense, Noah's Ark, and the Great Scenic Railway Roller Coaster, circa 1915 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Coney Island, view of the Boardwalk, including the Ward Baths, Coast Baths, Feltman's Garden, and Stauch's, circa 1920 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - View of Coney Island showing the House of Nonsense, Noah's Ark, and the Great Scenic Railway Roller Coaster, circa 1915 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Kiddie Land and Joe's Restaurant, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Looking East on Surf Avenue, 1926 [later copyprint] (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Luna Park and Surf Avenue, 1912 [later copyprint] (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Sea Wall, South of Concourse, Coney Island, February19, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Welfare Works Division Workers at work near Half Moon Hotel between Twenty-fifth and Twenty-seventh Streets, Coney Island Boardwalk, circa 1930 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Winter on Graves End Bay, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Personalities
      - Carte-postale of W. F. Mangels, Humphrey, and Harry C. Baker, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Children's choir at St. Paul's Lutheran Church, Brooklyn, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Crowning of Herman Raub, President of Consumers Park Brewery, as King of Mardi Gras at Coney Island, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Elmer 'Skip' Dundy and Frederick W. Thompson, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Elmer 'Skip' Dundy, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Eldorado at Coney Island undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Frederick W. Thompson, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Fredericak W. Thompson, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - George C. Tilyou, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - L.A. Thompson, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - William F. Mangels and the miniature sailboat ride, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - L. A. Thompson with children riding The Whirl-Over-Swing at Thompson Park, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Mr. Meinch (Mangels’ foreman) working on a Mardi Gras float, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Frederick W. Thompson, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - L. A. Thompson, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Samuel W. Gumpertz, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified woman, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified woman and dog, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - William F. Mangels within the Aero-Locomotive of his design, undesign (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - William F. Mangels, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Coney Island Chamber of Commerce and planners of the annual Mardi Gras celebration, William F. Mangels, Dr. Phillip Nash, William Meinch, Samuel W. Gumpertz, W. Ward, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - William F. Mangels at the Smithsonian Institution’s National Museum of Natural History (Washington, D.C.), undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Pools, baths and playgrounds
      - Playground at Forest Park (Kansas City, Missouri), 1903 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Giant slide and pool (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Exercises at Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths (Coney Island, New York), circa 1925 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Kiddie Pool at Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths, circa 1925 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Lucy Balmer's Great Atlantic Bathing & Swimming Pavilion (Coney Island, New York), before 1911 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Lucy Balmer's Great Atlantic Bathing & Swimming Pavilion (Coney Island, New York), before 1911 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Ping Pong tables at Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths (Coney Island, New York), circa 1925 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Pool [Ravenhall’s?] (Coney Island, New York), circa 1930 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Ravenhall's Handball Contest (Coney Island, New York), circa 1930 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths (Coney Island, New York), circa 1930 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths (Coney Island, New York), circa 1930 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Ravenhall's Bathing Park and Baths (Coney Island, New York), 1935 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Stauch's Dancing Pavilion (Coney Island, New York), undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - The pool in the Kiddies Park (Coney Island, New York), 1924 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Rides
      - Fat Lady on The Whip, Luna Park (Coney Island, New York), circa 1925 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - A Trip Through the Breakers, undated (3 images) (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Auto Polo Ride (Coney Island, New York), June 1925 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Auto Speedway, Rocking Park (Long Island, New York), undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Carousel or bicycle ride, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Caterpillar (Coney Island, New York) 1931 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Children on Zeppelin Ride, circa 1920 (Box 8, Folder 10)